Now its your turn to build the temperature unit setting. This
will bring together a lot of the concepts that you've learned and
will take some time to implement, but we think you're ready for
it. Modify the app, so that the right temperature units are displayed
to the user. Use the assumption that we're syncing metric data from
the server. Eventually, we'll have a database on the device and we
don't want a mix of Fahrenheit and Celsius data in there. Hence,
we'll stay consistent by getting metric data from the server. And then,
we'll convert on the fly to the preferred units when
we update the UI. After you make these changes, I'll show
you what it looks like on the device. If you
go to settings, you'll see the temperature units preference. If you
tap on that, you see a dialog with two options.
If you switch to imperial and then you go back to
the forecast list, then you see that all the temperatures now
are in Fahrenheit. Once it works, answer this question. Which subclass
of preference did you use?